http://www.heavengames.com/privacystatement.shtml

RSS
Main Portal Age of Empires Age of Empires 3 Age of Kings Age of Mythology Age of Wonders Age of Wonders 2 Battle for Middle Earth 2 Caesar 3 Caesar 4 Children of the Nile Emperor:RotMK Empire at War Empire Earth Empire: Total War Empires: DotMW Medieval 2: Total War Napoleon: Total War Pharaoh Rise & Fall:CaW Rise of Legends Rise of Nations Rome: Total War Stronghold Stronghold 2 SW:Galactic Battlegrounds Total War: Shogun 2 Zeus
Privacy Statement
HeavenGames has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate
our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information
gathering and dissemination practices for HeavenGames.
Information Automatically Logged
HeavenGames uses your IP address to help diagnose problems
with our server and to administer our Web site. Our server software
automatically logs all accesses to materials located on our servers.
This information remains private to persons associated with HeavenGames.
Consumer Information
During the process of visiting our websites, HeavenGames does
not automatically collect any personally identifiable information
about you such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address.
However, HeavenGames does obtain some types of non-personally identifiable
information such as the Internet Service Provider you use to connect
to the Internet, your browser type, or the type of computer operating
system you use (Macintosh or Windows, for example). The information
collected by HeavenGames is used for the purpose of generating demographic
data about our visitors.
Data Collection
HeavenGames, as well as many other sites on the Internet, use
"cookies" to enhance your experience on the web. We cannot
use these cookies to personally identify you in any way. What are
cookies and why do we use them? A cookie is a piece of data that
is stored on your computer at certain times during your visits to
a website. This unique data may later be recovered from your computer
in order to personalize your internet experience. This cookie can
help advertisers understand what you like and don't like about their
offerings so that they can cater better to your needs the next time
you are interested in their products or services.
Furthermore, we use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site.
These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address,
email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in
order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you
would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not
having this information used by these companies,
click here.
Public Forums
This site makes forums, downloads, articles and/or news available
to its users. Please remember that any information that you choose
to disclose while registering to use these areas becomes public
information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose
any personal information.  HeavenGames does not and will not
sell the information collected to any third parties.
Contests
HeavenGames will occassionally run contests on our site in which
we ask visitors for personal information (like name, email and mailing
address). This contact information is used only to get in touch
with the visitor when necessary and is destroyed upon the completion
of the contest.
External Links
This site contains links to other sites. HeavenGames is not responsible
for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
Security
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss,
misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Should
in any event, any information (such as access logs) be made available
to a third party, we will make the best effort to track it and report
the accident to proper authorities. We cannot be held accountable
for any misuse of such information.
Contacting HeavenGames
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the
practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you
can contact: info@heavengames.com
See also: Disclaimer
Copyright © 1997–2020 HeavenGames LLC.
All Rights Reserved.Please read our Disclaimer and Privacy Statement.
